asseenontvnetwork.com 2011-10-12

# Television Infomercial Products - As Seen On TV Network - Buxton Organizer Bag, Aqua Globes...

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Information You Provide to Us**  
We collect and store information that you voluntarily provide to us when you purchase a product, respond to a survey, and sign up for a promotion or enter a contest sponsored by the Site.  When you purchase a product, you provide your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and credit card information in order to complete the transaction.  If you enter a contest or sign up for a promotion, you provide your name and email address.

___back to top_

**Information that is Automatically Collected**   
When you access our Site, our web server automatically collects and stores your domain name, the date and time you access our Site.

_back to top_

**Use of Cookies and Storage of InformAsSeenOnTVNetwork.com is committed to providing the best products and friendliest customer service for the use of our site. Please note that AsSeenOnTVNetwork.com is a third party vendor of products and is not responsible for the manufacturing or distribution of the product but will do our best to help resolve issues where we can by forwarding complaints, questions or concerns to the proper parties. Please refer to your confirmation emails for customer service requests or fill out the form below to contact us. ation**  
We use cookies to collect and store information.  Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.  Cookies permit the Site to identify you.

_back to top_

**How We Use Your Information**  
The Company uses the information it collects from you in a variety of ways including to process your purchase transaction, to improve the content of your Site to address your preferences and to attract new users, to track user trends and patterns on the Internet so that we may inform users about products and services that may be of interest to them and, in some instances, to properly credit third parties that have referred you to the Site.  Stored information is also used to pre-populate information fields for purchases, contests or promotions.

The Company shares individual information with other reputable organizations includes its affiliates, its advertisers, its marketing partners and network advertising companies that are interested in marketing to Site users.  The Company and its advertisers and marketing partners use this information to ensure that ads, offers and promotions are relevant and of value to you.  Advertisers who contract directly with us are required to represent that they comply with our privacy policy with respect to information about your visit to our Site (and other websites) including what banner as was shown, the date and time it was shown, the cookie and the IP address.  This information may also be used for online preference marketing purposes.  Visit Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI�?) gateway opt-out site to review the privacy policies of network advertising companies and/or opt-out of network advertising cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

The Company reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time.

_back to top_

**How We Protect Your Information**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of personal information, the Company uses appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information including the use of firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.  All transmissions of information are through secure computer servers, which also run authentication and Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL�?) 128-bit software data encryption software to encrypt all personal information including your name, address and credit card number so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

_back to top_

 **Children’s Privacy Statement**  
In general, the Site does not direct its activities or market products appropriate for children under the age of 13.  It is the policy of the Company to refrain from knowingly collecting personally identifiable information from children age 12 or under.

_back to top_
